<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LabourAlert</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="settings">Setting</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="alert_no_internet">No internet connection try again later !</string>

    <!-- AdMob ad unit IDs -->
    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-8785326228290155~7489316207</string>
    <string name="banner_home_footer">ca-app-pub-3850953899146070/9603700155</string>
    <string name="interstitial_full_screen">ca-app-pub-3850953899146070/5022576878</string>
    <string name="rewarded_video">ca-app-pub-8785326228290155/4315879023</string>
    <!-- AdMob ad unit IDs -->

    <!--Common Alert Msg-->
    <string name="alert_message_error">Something went wrong please try after sometime.</string>
    <string name="alert_network_error">Network error! Try after sometime.</string>
    <string name="alert_some_error">Something went wrong, try again</string>
    <string name="alert_no_connection">No internet connection</string>

    <!--Splash Screen Strings-->
    <string name="labour_alerts">LABOUR ALERTS</string>
    <string name="labouralerts_com_is_a_service_that_allow_users_to_receive_alerts_about_employment_loss_notificaiton_near_you">
        Labouralerts.com is a service that allow users to receive alerts about employment loss notificaiton near you.
    </string>
    <string name="log_in">LOG IN</string>
    <string name="view_results">VIEW RESULTS</string>
    <!--Splash Screen Strings-->

    <!--Login Screen Strings-->
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="_login_small">Log In</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <!--Login Screen Strings-->


    <!--Subscription Screen Strings-->
    <string name="system_features">System features:</string>
    <string name="unlimited_mobile_and_website_advanced_access">- Unlimited mobile and website advanced access.</string>
    <string name="search_nationwide_database">- Search nationwide database.</string>
    <string name="create_email_and_mobile_notifications">- Create email and mobile notifications.</string>
    <string name="mobile_or_website_charts_and_graphs">- Mobile or website Charts and Graphs.</string>
    <string name="subscription_options">Subscription Options:</string>
    <string name="free_14_days_trial">Free 14 Days Trial</string>
    <string name="one_time_free_trial">One Time Free Trial</string>
    <string name="mobile_access">Mobile Access</string>
    <string name="_159_monthly">$159 Monthly</string>
    <string name="quaterly_acess">Quaterly Acess</string>
    <string name="_249_every_3_months">$249 every 3 months</string>
    <string name="_6_months_access">6 Months Access</string>
    <string name="_399_every_6_months">$419 every 6 months</string>
    <string name="yearly_access">Yearly Access</string>
    <string name="_799_every_12_months">$849 every 12 months</string>
    <string name="more_details">More Details</string>
    <string name="restore_purchases">Restore Purchases</string>
    <!--Subscription Screen Strings-->

    <!--Drawer Layout String-->
    <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_advanced_search">Advanced Search</string>
    <string name="menu_top_10">Top 10</string>
    <string name="title_top_10">Top 10 This Month</string>
    <string name="menu_alert_notification">Alert Notification</string>
    <string name="menu_alert_manager">Alert Manager</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_account">Account</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="menu_terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="menu_log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="labor_alerts">Labor Alerts</string>
    <string name="menu_upgrade_account">Upgrade Account</string>

    <!--Drawer Layout String-->

    <!--Search Option String-->
    <string name="label_company_city_state">Company, city or state</string>
    <string name="label_search">Search</string>
    <string name="label_advance_search">Advance Search</string>
    <!--Search Option String-->

    <!--Account Screen Strings-->
    <string name="label_subscription">Subscription</string>
    <string name="label_advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="label_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="label_update_password">Update Password:</string>
    <string name="hint_current_password">Current Password</string>
    <string name="hint_new_password">New Password</string>
    <string name="hint_re_validate_password">Re-Validate Password</string>
    <string name="hint_password_must_contain_1_upper_case_1_number_and_1_symbol">Password must contain: 1 Upper case, 1
        number and 1 Symbol
    </string>
    <string name="label_chnage_password">Change Password</string>
    <!--Account Screen Strings-->


    <!--Advanced Search Screen Strings-->
    <string name="label_company">Company</string>
    <string name="hint_company">Company</string>
    <string name="label_states">States</string>
    <string name="hint_states">States</string>
    <string name="label_years">Years</string>
    <string name="label_months">Months</string>
    <string name="hint_start">Start</string>
    <string name="hint_end">End</string>
    <string name="label_city">City</string>
    <string name="hint_city">City</string>
    <string name="label_country">Country</string>
    <string name="hint_country">Country</string>
    <!--Advanced Search Screen Strings-->

    <!--Alert Manager Screen String-->
    <string name="label_gm_lordstown_closure">GM Lordstown Closure</string>
    <!--Alert Manager Screen String-->

    <!--Search result screen-->
    <string name="label_result">Result</string>
    <string name="label_graph">Graph</string>
    <!--Search result screen-->

    <!--Sign up screen string-->
    <string name="hint_confirm_email">Confirm Email</string>
    <string name="hint_by_tapping_sign_up_amp_accept_you_agree_to_the_terms_of_service_and_privacy_policy">
        <![CDATA[By tapping Sign Up & Accept, you agree to the <font color=\\'#53b9e9\\'>Terms of Service</font> and <font color=\\'#53b9e9\\'>Privacy Policy</font>.]]></string>
    <string name="label_sign_up_amp_accept"><![CDATA[Sign Up & Accept]]></string>
    <!--Sign up screen string-->

    <!--Top 10 screen string-->
    <string name="label_companies">Companies</string>
    <string name="label_1y">1Y</string>
    <string name="label_3m">3M</string>
    <string name="label_2m">2M</string>
    <string name="label_1m">1M</string>
    <string name="label_send">Send</string>
    <string name="label_go_to_sign_in">Go To Sign In</string>
    <!--Top 10 screen string-->

    <!--About Us screen string-->
    <string name="lable_version">Version</string>
    <string name="label_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="label_terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <!--About Us screen string-->

    <!--TC PP and About us string-->
    <string name="about_us">This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their \'Personally identifiable information\' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

        What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

        We do not collect information from visitors of our site.
        or other details to help you with your experience.

        When do we collect information?

        We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form or enter information on our site.


        How do we use your information?

        We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

        • To personalize user\'s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
        • To improve our website in order to better serve you.
        • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
        • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
        • To quickly process your transactions.
        • To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
        • To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

        How do we protect visitor information?

        Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

        We use regular Malware Scanning.

        Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

        We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

        All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

        Do we use \'cookies\'?

        Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer\'s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site\'s or service provider\'s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

        We use cookies to:
        • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
        • Keep track of advertisements.
        • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

        You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser\'s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

        If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won\'t affect the user\'s experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

        However, you can still place orders .


        Third-party disclosure

        Do we disclose the information we collect to Third-Parties?
        We sell,trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your name, address,city,town, others
        Email
        personally identifiable information.


        Third-party links

        Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

        Google

        Google\'s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google\'s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

        We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

        Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google\'s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

        We have implemented the following:
        • Remarketing with Google AdSense
        • Google Display Network Impression Reporting
        • Demographics and Interests Reporting

        We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

        Opting out:
        Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

        California Online Privacy Protection Act

        CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law\'s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

        According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
        Users can visit our site anonymously.
        Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
        Our Privacy Policy link includes the word \'Privacy\' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

        Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
        • On our Privacy Policy Page
        Users are able to change their personal information:
        • By logging in to their account

        How does our site handle do not track signals?
        We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

        Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
        It\'s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

        COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

        When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children\'s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation\'s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children\'s privacy and safety online.

        We do not specifically market to children under 13.

        Fair Information Practices

        The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

        In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
        We will notify the users via email
        • Within 7 business days

        We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.</string>
    <string name="tc">TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE AGREEMENT :

        Hello and welcome to the Website of Laboralerts.com hereafter referred to hereinafter as “Laboralerts.com”, “We” or “Website”.

        We have drafted this Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement referred to hereinafter as the “Terms” so that you can understand your rights and obligations relating to the use of the Website.

        TERMS OF USE :

        By accessing the Website or creating an account on our Website you acknowledge and agree to these Terms and Conditions of Use and to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree with these Terms and Conditions of Use, we kindly ask you not to access or use this website.
        Violations of these Terms and Conditions of Use may result in termination of your account with or without notice. Users of this website should also read our privacy policy.

        AUTHORIZATION FOR MONTHLY RECURRING CREDIT CARD CHARGE :

        I authorize laboralets.com to charge my credit card account on a monthly basis for amounts I owe. I understand that this authorization is valid until either this authorization or provided services are canceled. I also understand this authorization is for the established monthly rate only, and that payment of additional work is not included in this authorization. I agree to notify laboralets.com of any changes to my credit card account information. I also agree that electronically transmitted copies of this agreement shall be deemed to be the original.

        CONTACT US :

        To contact Laboralerts.com or to obtain a copy of these terms or the privacy police please contact us at admin@laboralerts.com

        3rd Party :
        We are a website that compiles publically available information on government websites regarding the WARN ACT.
        We do not create the information regarding the warm act ourselves and therefore any reliability is based on government data. Business are required to file under some instances to post information regarding future layoffs or firings “Firing Information” in accordance WARN ACT notice reporting requirements as determine by state and federal laws. Our service only compiles this public Firing Information provided by State and local government. We are not affiliated with any government organization, any company, and have no affiliation to the Warn act. Any Firing Information regarding a given Business is derived from the public domain, and all information is provided as is without any guarantees (See our full disclaimers below). If you are a Business, and your Firing Information is posted on this website, we have acquired this information from the public domain, and is not in any way related to your compliance with the WARN ACT. We are not liable for any misinformation or government omission.

        UPDATES :

        We regularly update and alter the content of this website and can at anytime delete or change any information or services provided. We cannot guarantee to keep all information on this website complete and accurate. All information is provided as is.
        We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify these terms at any time by posting a notice on the Website, or by sending you a notice via email. You are solely responsible for reviewing and becoming familiar with any such modifications to the Terms. Such modifications to the Terms are effective immediately upon first posting or notification, and any subsequent use of our website subsequent to such posting or notification constitutes your acceptance of these Terms as modified.

        USER CONTENT AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY :

        Unless We agree otherwise in a written statement, any submission of content, including without limitation; any contributions, or other materials submitted directly through the Website (collectively, "Materials"); is hereby granted by you to the Website in the form of a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, non-exclusive, fully transferable and sub licensable right and license to access, store, copy, modify, use, and otherwise exploit all Materials in any form.

        We do not permit users to upload to its website any Materials which could infringe any rights of third parties. It is strongly prohibited to post defamatory comments, untrue statements, libel of any kind, any racist or unlawful purposes, as well as any violation of any copyright, trademark or service mark, and including the use of images for any subjects which could be considered offensive or abusive.

        You will be solely responsible for any punitive damages resulting from content that you post that constitutes intellectual property infringement, libel, defamation, from third parties and/or Laboralerts.com that may violate any laws or statutes whatsoever.

        We reserve the right to remove any user account without prior notice to the user and without having to justify it to the user.

        COPYRIGHTS :

        All content of this website including designs, text, graphics, pictures, video, information, software, code, logos, trademarks and service marks and other content and materials posted on this website, and their selection and arrangement (the “Site Materials”) are property of the Website and its affiliates and licensors with all rights reserved. You may not reuse or redistribute any part of the Website for any reason. Please do not copy or reproduce any portion of the Website without our expressed written permission.

        COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT :

        We are committed to complying with copyright and related laws. You are not allowed to store or transmit any material or content on the Website in any manner, if the material or content constitutes an infringement of third party intellectual property rights. It is our policy to terminate privileges of any User who infringe upon the intellectual property rights of others.

        DMCA COMPLIANCE :

        If you are the owner of a copyrighted work who believes your rights have been infringed please provide the Laboralerts.com Copyright Agent with the following information:

        1. An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright or other intellectual property interest;
        2. A specific description of the copyrighted work or other intellectual property that you claim has been infringed;
        3. A specific description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the Website, with enough detail that we may find it on the web site;
        4. Your address, telephone number, and email address;
        5. A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized;
        6. A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright or intellectual property owner or authorized to act on the copyright or intellectual property owner\'s behalf.

        CONTACT HERE :
        admin@laboralerts.com
        When we receive a proper notice of claimed infringement under the Digital Millennium Copyright act of 1998 (DMCA), the procedures specified in the DMCA will be followed to resolve the claim.

        NOT AN OFFICIAL WEBSITE :

        ALL INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE PROVIDED “AS – IS”. ALL INFORMATION, WITHOUT LIMITATION, INFORMATION POSTED ON THE WEBSITE REGARDING THE WARN ACT, EMPLOYERS NOTIFICATION DUTIES, FIRINGS, LAYOFFS, OR ANY OTHER MATERIALS WHATSOEVER IA NOT OFFICIAL AND SHOULD NEVER BE RELIED UPON FOR ANY PURPOSE. WE DO NOT HAVE ANY GOVERNMENT ENDORSEMENT OR CONNECTION TO ANY COMPANY THAT MUST COMPLY WITH THE WARN ACT. THIS WEBSITE IS NOT A SUBSTITIUION OR REPLACEMENT FOR OFFICIAL GOVERNMENT WEBSITES AND CANNOT BE USED TO FULFILL WARN ACT LAYOFF NOTIFICATIONS. FOR INFORMATION ON THE WARN ACT I. ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIALS ON THE WEBSITE ARE USED AT YOUR OWN RISK! PLEASE READ THE DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY AND NO WARRANTIES SECTION FOR OUR FULL DISCLAIMERS.

        NO WARRANTIES :

        ALL SERVICES, PRODUCTS, ACCOUNTS, PROFILES AND MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS” AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. WE MAKE NO WARRANTIES, EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, AND HEREBY DISCLAIM AND NEGATE ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, CORRECTNESS OF RESULTS, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OR OTHER VIOLATION OF RIGHTS.

        FURTHER, LABORALERTS.COM DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS CONCERNING THE ACCURACY, VALIDITY, LEGITAMACY, COMPENSATION, SAFETY, OUTCOME, LIKELY RESULTS, OR RELIABILITY OF ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION: MATERIALS POSTED ON THE WEBSITE, INFORMATION RELAYED BY THE WEBSITE OR ANY NEGATIVE EXPERIENCE WITH THE USE OF ANY INFORMATION LISTED ON THE WEBSITE WHATSOEVER, AND ALL OTHER ASSOCIATED MATERIALS ON THE WEBSITE OR ON ANY SITES LINKED TO OR FROM THE WEBSITE.

        NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY YOU FROM THE WEBSITE OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER.

        LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY :

        YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT LABORALERTS.COM; ITS OWNERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES AND AFFILIATES, IN NO CASE SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGES RELATED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY TO THE USE OF THE WEBSITE OR THROUGH THE USE OF ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE SOLD ON THE WEBSITE.

        YOU AGREE TO DEFEND, INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS THE WEBSITE, LABORALERTS.COM; AND ANY PARENT, SUBSIDIARY, AFFILIATE, DIRECTOR, OFFICER, EMPLOYEE, LICENSOR, DISTRIBUTOR, SUPPLIER, AGENT, RESELLER, OWNER, OR OPERATOR OF LABORALERTS.COM FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, OBLIGATIONS, LOSSES, LIABILITIES, COSTS OR DEBT, AND EXPENSES INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO; ATTORNEY’S FEES, DEMANDS, TRAVEL EXPENSES, OBLIGATIONS, DAMAGES (ACTUAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL, INCLUDING LOST PROFIT DAMAGES, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER OR NOT YOU HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), COSTS, AND EXPENSES AND ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY OF ANY KIND OR NATURE WHATSOEVER, WHETHER KNOWN OR UNKNOWN, SUSPECTED OR UNSUSPECTED, DISCLOSED OR UNDISCLOSED, THAT YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST US OR THEM ARISING FROM THE FOLLOWING, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION: (I) YOUR USE OF AND ACCESS TO LABORALERTS.COM; (II) YOUR VIOLATION OF ANY TERM OF THESE TERMS OF USE; (III) USE OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, DESCRIPTIONS OR ACCOUNTS; (IV) ANY REASON WHATSOEVER NOT EXPLICITLY AFOREMENTIONED. THIS DEFENSE AND INDEMNIFICATION OBLIGATION WILL SURVIVE THESE TERMS OF USE AND YOUR USE OF WEBSITE.

        THE ABSOLUTE MAXIMUM LIABILITY ACCORDING TO THIS TERMS AND CONDITIONS AGREEMENT FOR ANY CAUSE WHATSOEVER SHALL NOT EXCEED $5.00 (FIVE DOLLARS).

        CLAIMS AND CAUSE OF ACTION LIMITATIONS :

        YOU AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT USE OF OR RELATED IN ANY WAY TO THE WEBSITE OR THE TERMS MUST COMMENCE WITHIN SIX MONTHS AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION; OTHERWISE, ANY SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION IS WAIVED AND PERMANENTLY BARRED.

        LEGAL USE :

        Although you may access this Website from other territories around the world, by accessing this website you agree that its use, the use of any material contained on the website and the use of all services provided, will be governed by the laws and courts of Wyoming, regardless of where you live, or how these laws may differ from the laws of the country from which you are accessing this website.

        You may use this website only in accordance with these Terms and Conditions of Use and only for lawful purposes as stipulated by applicable law. You may not abuse this website in any way or use any automated software when accessing and using this website.



        You may not use this website in any manner that violates any law, regulation, treaty or tariff or infringes on the legal rights of any third party, or in any manner which is defamatory, fraudulent, indecent, unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another\'s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable. You may not post content that is offensive or deceptive, to threaten, harass, abuse or intimidate others, to damage the name or reputation of the Website, its affiliates, or subsidiaries, or to access an account that does not belong to you, and in any manner whatsoever which interferes with other customers\' use of services provided by the Website.

        You are prohibited from storing, posting, distributing or transmitting any unlawful content at or through this Website or otherwise in connection with the Terms and Conditions of Use. Examples of unlawful content include but are not limited to direct threats of physical harm, stalking, copyrighted, trademarked and other proprietary material used without permission. Additional prohibited content includes but is not limited to: programs containing Trojan horses, virus and/or tools to compromise the security of this website and/or other sites, suggestions or encouragement of illegal activity, duplicative posting, “phishing”, “spimming” or "spamming".

        Children and individuals under the age of 18 years are allowed use of this website only under supervision and with consent of their parents or legal representatives. By using the website without supervision; or by registering an account with the Website, you warrant that you are at least 18 years of age and have full legal capacity, or that you have consent from your parents or legal guardians to use the Website. If you are under the age of 13, we ask that you please not use the Website under any circumstances.

        MISCELLANEOUS :

        The Website may be viewed internationally and may contain references to products or services not available in all countries. References to a particular product or service do not imply that such product or service is appropriate or available to all persons of legal purchasing age in all locations, or that we intend to make such product or service available in such locations.
        ANY OFFER FOR ANY SERVICE MADE ON WEBSITE IS VOID WHERE PROHIBITED.

        NO WAIVERS :

        Our failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of this Agreement or Terms of Use shall not operate as a waiver of such right or provision.
        Our performance under these Terms of Use is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in these Terms of Use is in derogation of our right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requirements with regards to your use of The Website or information, products or services provided or gathered by use for such use as it relates to our performance.

        SEVERABILITY AND ENFORCEABILITY :

        If any provision or portion of these Terms of Use is held illegal, invalid, or unenforceable, in whole or in part, it shall be modified to the minimum extent necessary to correct any deficiencies or replaced with a provision which is as close as is legally permissible to the provision found invalid or unenforceable and the replacement, if any, shall not affect the legality, validity or enforceability of any other provisions or portions of these Terms of Use, and all other provisions of the Terms and Conditions shall remain in full force and effect.

        CHOICE OF LAW :

        These Terms of Use will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Wyoming, without regard to its conflicts of law provisions. You hereby agree that any cause of action you may have with respect to Laboralerts.com must be filed in a court located in Wyoming.

        ASSIGNABILITY :

        These Terms of Use and your account on the Website are personal to you and for your sole use, and may not be transferred or assigned.

        NO CLASS ACTION :

        You agree no claim subject to the Terms may be brought as a class action.

        SECTION TITLES :

        The section titles used in this Agreement are for the purposes of convenience and carry no legal or contractual effect.

        TERMINATION :

        In the event there is a termination of this Agreement for any reason, you agree the following provisions will survive the termination: Use of Content, Limitations of Liability, No Warranties.

        CONFLICTS :

        In the event there is a conflict between these terms of use and the terms of use of any any other device terms or policy (for example, a mobile device terms of use or a P3P electronic privacy policy), these Terms of Use shall control. Furthermore, in case of a conflict between these Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy, these Terms of Use shall control.
    </string>
    <string name="pp">This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their \'Personally identifiable information\' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

        What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

        We do not collect information from visitors of our site.
        or other details to help you with your experience.

        When do we collect information?

        We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, fill out a form or enter information on our site.


        How do we use your information?

        We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

        • To personalize user\'s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
        • To improve our website in order to better serve you.
        • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
        • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
        • To quickly process your transactions.
        • To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
        • To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

        How do we protect visitor information?

        Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

        We use regular Malware Scanning.

        Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

        We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

        All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

        Do we use \'cookies\'?

        Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer\'s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site\'s or service provider\'s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

        We use cookies to:
        • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
        • Keep track of advertisements.
        • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

        You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser\'s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

        If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won\'t affect the user\'s experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

        However, you can still place orders .


        Third-party disclosure

        Do we disclose the information we collect to Third-Parties?
        We sell,trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your name, address,city,town, others
        Email
        personally identifiable information.


        Third-party links

        Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

        Google

        Google\'s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google\'s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

        We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

        Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google\'s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

        We have implemented the following:
        • Remarketing with Google AdSense
        • Google Display Network Impression Reporting
        • Demographics and Interests Reporting

        We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

        Opting out:
        Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

        California Online Privacy Protection Act

        CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law\'s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

        According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
        Users can visit our site anonymously.
        Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
        Our Privacy Policy link includes the word \'Privacy\' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

        Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
        • On our Privacy Policy Page
        Users are able to change their personal information:
        • By logging in to their account

        How does our site handle do not track signals?
        We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

        Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
        It\'s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

        COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

        When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children\'s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation\'s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children\'s privacy and safety online.

        We do not specifically market to children under 13.

        Fair Information Practices

        The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

        In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
        We will notify the users via email
        • Within 7 business days

        We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.</string>
    <!--TC PP and About us string-->

</resources>
